The Secret is Out!
Hey, Dad! Do you know what day it is tomorrow?
Tell me, what day is it tomorrow? 🎵
Did you forget? I'll give you a hint, it's-
Is it our son's turn to do the chores?
No, no, it's something more special than-
Is it time for spring cleaning?
Your room is getting pretty messy after all.
I would appreciate it if you could clean the garage and mow the lawn while you're at it. Eh?
Ugh... Tch.
Vera!
What are you looking at?
Jun!
Huh?! Jun?
Wait, Vera... do you have a crush on...
No!
I'm just keeping an eye on him. I'm going to find out his secret!
Secret?
Yes! It's something so top secret that even FBI agents would be rushing after him!
You'd better watch out!
Top secret...?
Metal Breath, pickup...
Mega Trucker, setup...
Now, come at me!
That was good!
With a few tweaks here and there, I think I can make your shield even stronger.
Huh, really? Then let's do it right now!
It's not that easy. The stronger the shield, the more energy it's gonna consume, you know?
What if it stops working when you need it the most?
Come back, Mega Trucker!
I'll be off now, Uncle Edo...
What? Leaving so soon?
It's my turn to do the chores, ahaha...
What's got him acting so strange?
A secret? Jun's keeping one?
Mhm. Do you know anything?
Oh, uh...
Attack!
Punch!
You got this, Blue Cop!
Sealing complete!
It's not like he doesn't have any secrets, but...
What is it, Theo?! Tell me!
A-actually...
Actually?
Well, Jun is...
Yeah?
It's his birthday today!
Oh-aha! That was it?
Y-Yeah, that's it.
Oh, Theo, you should have told me sooner! I was worried over nothing!
In that case, we should go celebrate!
Celebrate?
Yes! We should get a cake and go to Jun's house right now!
S-shouldn't we call him and let him know we're coming?
But that's no fun! I'm sure Jun would like a surprise party even more!
Oh no, this can only end badly...
It's my birthday, so why do I have to mow the lawn?!
Both Mom and Dad aren't showing any love for their son today.
Jun, whatcha doin'?
Can't you see? I'm mowing the lawn!
It looks fun! Let me try, let me try!
Wha...?
Woohoo!
Having fun?
Haha! This is the best!
Hey, Jun! Give me something to do too.
Haha! This is fun!
I'm happy if you guys are happy.
Jun.
What if someone sees them? We agreed to keep the Metal Cardbots a secret.
That's right, but...
Ah, Blue Cop! I have a job for you that'll keep everyone from being seen!
Yeah man, wasn't the food today just the-
Huh?
This street is currently closed. Please find a detour.
Let's just go to the internet cafe.
Yeah, let's go.
Should we really be doing this?
Relax. What's the worst that could happen?
Excuse me!
I'm sorry, but this area is off limits.
Huh?
Hi... I'm sorry, but we just need to cross the street.
Could you let us through?
But, uh... well, uh... What should I do?
Um...
Oh, it's you!
Perhaps... you could go ask the person in charge?
Oh, haha, right. Hold on a minute!
Okay, let him through!
What's up?
Theo came to visit.
Waah!
Hello!
H-Heyyy!
It's an emergency! Hurry, hurry, transform!
This is bad!
Sorry for dropping in like this. Is now a bad time?
Of course not! You guys are always welcome here!
I'm glad! What are you up to?
Uh... Just some yard work?
Wow! Can I see?
B-b-b-but Anna! I-It's not done yet!
Why is there a truck in your yard?
Uh, someone just asked me to take care of it!
Aah! Hey! Wait!
Why don't we-
Aah!
Shadow X, stealth mode on!
Stop that. What are you doing?
There was a huge bug!
Theo, you really hate bugs, right? I know how you get!
So Anna, what brings you here?
Oh, that's right!
There, you can open your eyes now.
Happy birthday, Jun!
Thank you, Anna! I never imagined you'd come to wish me a happy birthday!
Now, it's time to blow out the candles!
This is Blue Cop. Jun. Please respond.
What was that noise?
Right, that was..?
I-It must be the TV in the living room!
I think it's time we open the street back up. Would that be okay? Jun?
Jun?
I need a response!
Jun! Jun! Jun!
Ahaha! Theo, why do you keep calling my name?
H-happy birthday, Jun!
Jun! Why aren't you answering?
What? What's the matter?
Maybe he was taken hostage by robbers!
Jun! I'm on my way!
Blue Cop!
What was that?
It sounded like a car accident!
Anyway, let's blow out the candles!
Yes! Let's sing Happy Birthday now!
1, 2, 3!
Happy birthday to me...
What's happening?!
Now this looks really bad!
Don't just stand there, go give them a hand!
What do we do? Jun! Hurry, give us a command!
Jun?!
You're hiding something from me, aren't you?!
But... I...
That's it!
Ah, no! Anna!
Hello.
Aah!!
She just found out.
The secret is out...
So you guys are like...
refugees who came to Earth all the way from planet Machina at the other end of the galaxy?
Oh...
She's smart.
So, Anna. You'll help us keep these guys a secret, right?
I'm afraid I can't.
Huh? Why not?
Because, this is the first encounter between humanity and aliens.
This isn't something that kids should be handling.
But I'm a grown-up.
I'm sorry, Uncle Edo.
Apologizing just makes it sound worse...
Anna. We just want to live quietly on planet Earth.
Please understand.
It's not that I don't trust you. It's just that...
I don't have it in me to keep lying to the grown ups.
Hey, it's my dad!
Dad?
The father of this child.
A human who has grown up.
Among humans, Anna's father is pretty high-profile.
He's the mayor of Mowtown!
Shh!
Hello?
Anna, where are you right now?
He's asking where I am!
Why is he asking that?
Could it be... that he found out about us?
No, don't be ridiculous!
He's not a mind reader. How could he know?
No, no! My dad really knows everything!
He knew right away when I skipped piano practice, and when I broke a vase!
Yeah! Grown-ups know everything.
That's right. Lies won't work on them.
Hang on! You mean, the mayor already knows?
About the existence of Metal Cardbots on Earth?